<resources>
    <string name="app_name">sports_summary</string>
    <string name="txt">The English Premier League is the most popular championship in the world.But where did it all start?
The predecessor was the First Division, which existed since 1888. Having completed the 1990/91 campaign, the clubs came to the conclusion that in order to compete on the international stage, it is vital for the league to change.

Creating an organization
The boiling point and the point of no return came on July 17, 1991 - then all the participants of the First Division planned to withdraw from the league by signing the Founding Agreement. The essence of it is as follows: a new organization is being formed called the Premier League of the Football Association, at the disposal of which media rights and the ability to conclude sponsorship contracts without outside interference are transferred.On May 27, 1992, the Founding Agreement came into force — and 22 teams officially said goodbye to the Football League. Arsenal, Aston Villa, Blackburn Rovers, Chelsea, Coventry City, Crystal Palace, Everton, Ipswich Town, Leeds United, Liverpool, Manchester City, Manchester United, Middlesbrough, Norwich City, Nottingham Forest, Oldham Athletic, Queens Park Rangers, Sheffield United, Sheffield Wednesday, Southampton, Tottenham Hotspur and Wimbledon — all of these teams became co-founders of the Premier League.

As time has shown, the historical upheaval has benefited: having gained ground for development, English football has rapidly grown to 22 divisions. Starting with amateurs and ending with the cherry on this huge cake — the Premier League.

Today, the submarine is a huge, expensive kaleidoscope, attracting a billion—dollar audience. It seems that no one is able to shift its position — even the Spaniards, who have dominated the international arena in recent years. It is their brainchild that is important to the British — it is not for nothing that Pep Guardiola often says that Manchester City need, first of all, to assert themselves at home and only then look at the Champions League.</string>
</resources>